

Jimmy Cabuy

Web Developer • Digital Marketing Novice • Freelance Photographer

After graduating from EPHEC in e-business, I worked for over 2 years as a content creator, social media ads expert, and social media manager in a digital marketing agency. I then followed a web development Bootcamp in JavaScript to fulfil my dream of becoming a developer. Currently, I work at Decathlon Belgium as a front-end developer where I collabore to code, debug, troubleshoot, and enhance the website's user experience.

jimmycabuy@hotmail.com

Brussels

linkedin.com/in/jimmycabuy

+32/474.91.78.15

www.jimmycabuy.com/

github.com/jimmycabuy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer

Decathlon Belgium 🗷

06/2023 - Present

Brussels

Technical Consultant

Worldline 🗷

01/2023 - 06/2023 Financial Services Brussels

Brussels

Social Media Manager

Socialsky 🗷

02/2019 - 06/2021 Social Media Agency

Achievements/Tasks

- Management of our clients' social networks
- Digital Strategy
- Social Ads
- Community Management

EDUCATION

General Humanities

Mater Dei

09/2009 - 06/2015 Brussels

Certificate of English

Browns English Language School

10/2015 - 12/2015 Brisbane

Bachelor in e-Business

EPHEC 🗷

09/2016 - 06/2019 Brussels

Courses

Web DesignE-commerceWeb DevelopmentDigital Marketing

Business AnalystSupply Chain Management

Erasmus

ESSCA School of Management

08/2018 - 01/2019 Budapest

Web & Mobile Coding Bootcamp

La Capsule 🗷

03/2022 - 05/2022 Brussels

Courses

HTML / CSS / JavaScript
Express.js
MongoDB
UI Design
React.js
Node.js
Heroku
UX Design

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Uwork (03/2022 - 05/2022) 🗹

 Uwork is a mobile application that connects jobseekers with companies looking for employees. This application aims to totally democratize and review the hiring system with a simple and easy to use application.

Portfolio - thedailyjim 🗹

 In my spare time, I have another passion besides coding and another name: "thedailyjim" as a photographer. I've been passionate about the world of photography since I was young, and I love to get out of my house and capture the life and the surrounding landscapes.

Evidensy (11/2024) 🗹

 Designed and developed a custom showcase website for Evidensy, aligning with client needs and enhancing brand visibility.

TRAVELS

Australia (10/2015 - 05/2016)

America (07/2021 - 01/2022)

Canada, United-States, Mexico, Equator and Costa Rica

LANGUAGES

French English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

